Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Skyy - High; First time around, 1980; SR-30365; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 323 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-323-A-10 TERLING
        - Skyy - Superlove, 1980; SR-30366; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 344 (DJ); A-side Matrix # SG-344-A-1
        - Skyy - Skyyjammer, 1982; SR-30367; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SA 8555; A-side Matrix # SA 8555 A 2 ATLANTIC STUDIOS
        - Skyy - Skyyzoo, 1980; SR-30368; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 329; A-side Matrix # SG-329-C 10 1 STERLING A C
        - Skyy - Givin' it (To you), 1986; SR-30369; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # V-15226; A-side Matrix # V-1-15226-100154A-22 1 CSB MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK
        - Skyy - First time around, 1979; SR-30370; Skyy (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30371. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # SG 215 (DJ); A-side Matrix # SG-215-A-20 STERLING A 1 1 X
        - Skyy - First time around, 1979; SR-30371; Skyy (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30370. 2 copies.
        - Skyy - Dancin' to be dancin', 1984; SR-30372; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 430 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-430-A-1 A1 A STERLING
        - Skyy - Skyy flyy, 1982; SR-30373; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # A 120 167; A-side Matrix # 120 167-A
        - Skyy - Movin' violation; Get into the beat, 1982; SR-30374; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 380 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG 380 A-2 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Skyy - Non-stop, 1986; SR-30375; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # V-15251; A-side Matrix # V-1-15251-100157B-100157A-23
        - Skyy - Start of a romance, 1989; SR-30376; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # DMD 1303; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56616-56612-56614-3 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Skyy - Givin' it (To you), 1986; SR-30377; Skyy (Box 435)
        - Skyy - Married man, 1983; SR-30378; Skyy (Box 435)
          Catalog # SG 420; A-side Matrix # SG-420A-3
        - Skyywalker, Luke - Skyywalker's bass waves mega mixes, 1987; SR-30379; Skyywalker, Luke; Luke (Box 435)
        - Slacker - Your face, 1997; SR-30380; Slacker (Box 435)
          Catalog # XLT 87; A-side Matrix # XLT 87 A2 GUYS THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
          XL Recordings
        - Slade - Slam the hammer down, 1984; SR-30381; Slade (Box 435)
          Catalog # AS 1921; A-side Matrix # XSM 171957-1A
          CBS Associated Records
        - Slam Slam - Something ain't right, 1990; SR-30382; Slam Slam; Lee, Dee C. (Box 435)
          Catalog # MCA12 53968; A-side Matrix # MCA 10488 FDS-2 FUTURE DISC T.B.
        - Slanina, Stephan - Grand piano, 1994; SR-30383; Slanina, Stephan; Genetic Atmosfear (Box 435)
          Catalog # DOS 009-1; A-side Matrix # DOS 009-B
          Dos Or Die Recordings
          Krefeld, Germany
        - Slapbak - We come to jam, 1996; SR-30384; Slapbak (Box 435)
          Catalog # TR-7260-1; A-side Matrix # TR-7260-1-A F-1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
          Thug Records
          Encino, California
        - Slave - Steppin' out, 1983; SR-30385; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # DMD 694; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45257-1
        - Slave - Feel my love, 1980; SR-30386; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # DMD 273; A-side Matrix # STDM 39922 1 SM 1-1
        - Slave - Ooohh, 1984; SR-30387; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # DMD 789; A-side Matrix # STDM 47027-1 1-1 STERLING
        - Slave - Thrill me, 1986; SR-30388; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # 12-PO53; A-side Matrix # 12-PO53 A SMRP
          Ichiban Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Slave - Slave 88, 1988; SR-30389; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # ICH-1030; A-side Matrix # ICH-1030-A SP- 10-X-88 R100
        - Slave - Best of slave, 1984; SR-30390; Slave (Box 435)
          Catalog # 90182-1; A-side Matrix # ST CTN 845467 A E-1WS1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Sleeze Boyz - Robo cop, 1988; SR-30391; Sleeze Boyz (Box 435)
          Catalog # SRD-814; A-side Matrix # L 30940 ROBO-A L-724-SRD-814-A
          Sheik Records
        - Sleeze Boyz - Dance till you drop, 1989; SR-30392; Sleeze Boyz (Box 435)
          Catalog # SRD-814-RE1; A-side Matrix # SRD-814-RE-1-A S-21345
          Boss Man Recordings
        - Slice, Eli - Shake yo thing, 2000; SR-30393; Slice, Eli; Cash; Janei; Swift (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30394. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RNB001; A-side Matrix # RNB001-A
          Royal Blud Music
        - Slice, Eli - Shake yo thing, 2000; SR-30394; Slice, Eli; Cash; Janei; Swift (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30393. 2 copies.
        - Slick Rick - Behind bars, 1994; SR-30395; Slick Rick; Fresh, Doug E.; Nice & Smooth; Warren G (Box 435)
          Catalog # 314 523 847-1; A-side Matrix # 314-523-847-1-AS/HS MASTERDISK TD
        - Slick Rick - We turn it on, 1999; SR-30396; Slick Rick; Fresh, Doug E.; Raekwon (Box 435)
          Catalog # 314 562 125-1; A-side Matrix # 314-562-125-1-A HFM '99
        - Slim - It’s in the mix, 1982; SR-30397; Slim (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30398. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RC 502; A-side Matrix # RC 502 B STERLING PRESSED AT SOUND MAKERS N.J.
          D.E.T.T. Records
          Landover, Maryland
        - Slim - It’s in the mix, 1982; SR-30398; Slim (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30397. 2 copies.
        - Slim Thug - Like a boss, 2004; SR-30399; Slim Thug (Box 435)
          Catalog # GEFR 26161-1; A-side Matrix # GEFR-26161-1-A
        - Slim Thug - Already platinum (Chopped & screwed) (disc one), 2005; SR-30400; Slim Thug; Kyleon, Killa; Slick Pulla; Young Jeezy; Jazze Pha; Bun B; T.I.; Williams, Pharell; Pusha T (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30401. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005874-01; A-side Matrix # B0005874-01 A
        - Slim Thug - Already platinum (Chopped & screwed) (disc two), 2005; SR-30401; Slim Thug; Bun B; Killa Kyleon; Slick Pulla; Young Jeezy (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30400. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005874-01; A-side Matrix # B0005874-01 C
        - Slimline - If you can dance you can do it, 1982; SR-30402; Slimline (Box 435)
          Catalog # PRL D633; A-side Matrix # PRLD-633-AS A-2 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Slimm Calhoun - It's OK, 2000; SR-30403; Slimm Calhoun (Box 435)
          Catalog # ED-6226; A-side Matrix # ED-6226-A
        - Slimm Calhoun - Well, 2001; SR-30404; Slimm Calhoun; Killer Mike (Box 435)
          Catalog # ED 6260; A-side Matrix # MCR-RCE STE-6260 A-1
        - Slingshot - Do it again medley with Billie Jean, 1983; SR-30405; Slingshot (Box 435)
          Catalog # QUS 044; A-side Matrix # QUS-044-A
        - Slo Moshun - Help my friend, 1994; SR-30406; Slo Moshun (Box 435)
          Catalog # 44 77700; A-side Matrix # XSS-77700-A-1A RANDY M. Jr.
        - Slow Children - Slow children, 1982; SR-30407; Slow Children (Box 435)
          Catalog # NXL 1-8001; A-side Matrix # NXL 1-8001-A STERLING A1 D
          Ensign
        - Slow Children - President am I, 1982; SR-30408; Slow Children (Box 436)
          Catalog # JD-13236; A-side Matrix # JD-13236A A1
          London, united Kingdom
        - Slow Pain - Saturday night ballin', 1995; SR-30410; Slow Pain (Box 436)
          Catalog # TH 2223; A-side Matrix # S-32159 TH-2223-A
          Thump Records
          Walnut, California
        - Slow Pain - Money maid, 1996; SR-30411; Slow Pain (Box 436)
          Catalog # TH 2225; A-side Matrix # S-32670 TH-2225-A
        - Slow Pain - Slow pain baby (On the left, on the right), 1996; SR-30412; Slow Pain (Box 436)
          Catalog # TH2229-1; A-side Matrix # S-33174 TH-2229-A
        - Deep Freeze Productions - Slowbone (disc one), 1995; SR-30413; Deep Freeze Productions (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30414. Double album.
          Catalog # SSRLP001; A-side Matrix # SSR LP 001-A2 R-M Pauls @ PORKYS'
          Sure Shot Records
        - Deep Freeze Productions - Slowbone (disc two), 1995; SR-30414; Deep Freeze Productions (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30413. Double album.
          Catalog # SSRLP001; A-side Matrix # SSR LP 001-C1 PRE Pauls @ PORKYS'
        - Slug-Go - Live, 1987; SR-30415; Slug-Go (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30416. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TDE-LP-3029; A-side Matrix # TDE-3029-A MASTERWORK SMC
        - Slug-Go - Live, 1987; SR-30416; Slug-Go (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30415. 2 copies.
        - Slug-Go - Live, 1987; SR-30417; Slug-Go (Box 436)
          Catalog # TDE-LP-3029; A-side Matrix # TDE-LP-3029-A MASTERWORK
        - Slug-Go - Live, 1987; SR-30418; Slug-Go (Box 436)
        - Slug-Go - Crazy, 1985; SR-30419; Slug-Go (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30420. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TDE-3008; A-side Matrix # TDE-3008-A
        - Slug-Go - Crazy, 1985; SR-30420; Slug-Go (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30419. 2 copies.
        - Sly & Robbie - Sly-Robbie + the Taxi Gang v Purpleman + friends, 1983; SR-30421; Sly & Robbie; Taxi Gang; Purpleman (Box 436)
          Catalog # VSLP 4012; A-side Matrix # MPO VSLP 4012 A1
          Vista Sounds
          Burnt Oak, Edgware, United Kingdom
        - Sly & Robbie - Rhythm killers, 1987; SR-30422; Sly & Robbie; Collins, Bootsy; Berger, Karl (Box 436)
          Catalog # BRLP 512; A-side Matrix # BRLP 512 A-1U-1-2-
        - Sly & Robbie - Language barrier, 1985; SR-30423; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30424. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 90286-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL 855 711-B MASTERDISK 1-1
        - Sly & Robbie - Language barrier, 1985; SR-30424; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30423. 2 copies.
        - Sly & Robbie - Bass & trouble, 1985; SR-30425; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          Catalog # PRO-416; A-side Matrix # PRO-416-A MASTERDISK A-
        - Sly & Robbie - Nightnurse, 1998; SR-30426; Sly & Robbie; Simply Red (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30427. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 6080; A-side Matrix # STED-6080 A-1 F/W RCE
          EastWest
        - Sly & Robbie - Nightnurse, 1998; SR-30427; Sly & Robbie; Simply Red (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30426. 2 copies.
        - Sly & Robbie - Turbo charge, 1985; SR-30428; Sly & Robbie; Burrell, Roland; Brown, Dennis; Riley, Jimmy; Tamlins; Yellowman; Taxi Gang; Black Uhuru (Box 436)
          Catalog # TAXI 26; A-side Matrix # DSR-6856-A1-SPIDERMAN SONIC SOUNDS
          Taxi
        - Sly & Robbie - Crucial reggae - driven by Sly & Robbie, 1982; SR-30429; Sly & Robbie; The Mighty Diamonds; The Rolands; Lara, Derrick; Sly Dunbar; Floyd, Bobby; Brown, Dennis; Riley, Jimmy; Tamlins; Yellowman; Holt, Errol "Flabba"; Livingston, Carlton; Nooks, Geroge (Box 436)
          Catalog # MLPS 9730; A-side Matrix # MPLS-9730-A-RE1
          Mango
        - Sly & Robbie - Make 'em move; The Wrecking Crew theme, 1985; SR-30430; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          Catalog # PRO-425; A-side Matrix # PRO-425 A
        - Sly & Robbie - Boops (Here to go), 1987; SR-30431; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          Catalog # DMD 1023; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51264-1 MASTERDISK
        - Sly & Robbie - Yes we can can, 1987; SR-30432; Sly & Robbie (Box 436)
          Catalog # DMD 1077; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51569-1 MASTERDISK
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Dance to the music (Extended version), 1987; SR-30433; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          Catalog # SLY T1; A-side Matrix # SLYT-1-A1
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Dance to the music, 1971; SR-30434; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30435. 2 copies.
          Catalog # E 30334; A-side Matrix # XSB 136161-2A
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Dance to the music, 1971; SR-30435; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30434. 2 copies.
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Small talk, 1974; SR-30436; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30437. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PE 32930; A-side Matrix # P AL 32930-1F
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Small talk, 1974; SR-30437; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30436. 2 copies.
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Fresh, 1973; SR-30438; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          Catalog # KE 32134; A-side Matrix # AL32134-2A
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Different strokes by different folks, 2006; SR-30439; Sly & The Family Stone; Will I Am; Legend, John; Stone, Joss; Hunt, Van; Roots; Big Boi; Brown, Sleepy; Killer Mike; Chuck D.; D'Angelo; Hayes, Isaac; Jackson, Janet; DJ Reset (Box 436)
          Catalog # XPR8942; A-side Matrix # XPR 8942-A
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Stand!, 1986; SR-30440; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 436)
          Catalog # PE 26456; A-side Matrix # XSB 139307-2B SS
        - Sly Boogy - If you got crew, 2004; SR-30441; Sly Boogy; Jagged Edge (Box 436)
          Catalog # J12-62874-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-62874-1 SA
        - Sly Fox - Como tu te llama? (What is your name), 1985; SR-30442; Sly Fox (Box 436)
          Catalog # V-8654; A-side Matrix # V-1-8654-99675-A1B G-2 MASTERED BY CAPITOL
        - Sly Fox - Let's go all the way, 1985; SR-30443; Sly Fox (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30444. 2 copies.
          Catalog # V-8639; A-side Matrix # V18639-99669-B-Z1 2 STERLING
        - Sly Fox - Let's go all the way, 1985; SR-30444; Sly Fox (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30443. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO-9643; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9643-99669C-Z2 B-22818 Z2 11808 0- 2 SPAR MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Sly Stone - High on you, 1975; SR-30445; Sly Stone (Box 436)
          Catalog # PE 33835; A-side Matrix # PAL-33835-1AC
        - Sly Stone - Dance to the music; Sing a simple song, 1979; SR-30446; Sly Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30447. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AS 675; A-side Matrix # XSS-166672-1A STERLING
        - Sly Stone - Dance to the music; Sing a simple song, 1979; SR-30447; Sly Stone (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30446. 2 copies.
        - Slyde - We love it; Right on, 2005; SR-30448; Slyde (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30449. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FLR055; A-side Matrix # 58013 2B FLR 055 2ND TIME LUCKY
          Finger Lickin' Records
        - Slyde - We love it; Right on, 2005; SR-30449; Slyde (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30448. 2 copies.
        - Slyy, Ray - Hey you (You got to give it up), 1982; SR-30450; Slyy, Ray (Box 436)
          Catalog # SG 382 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-382-A-1 A C MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK
        - Small Fish With Spine - Stickleback, 1995; SR-30451; Small Fish With Spine (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30452. 2 copies.
          Catalog # OMWE006-1; A-side Matrix # OMWE 006 B
          OMW (Oxygen Music Works)
        - Small Fish With Spine - Stickleback, 1995; SR-30452; Small Fish With Spine (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30451. 2 copies.
        - Smash - Street walker, 1986; SR-30453; Smash; Grandmaster Melle Mel (Box 436)
          Catalog # PR 0120; A-side Matrix # 0120 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK CSB
          Paran
        - Smith, Brad - How y'all feel out there, 2000; SR-30454; Smith, Brad (Box 436)
          Catalog # PP002; A-side Matrix # PP-002-A F/W G V
          Painted Puppy Productions
          Tampa, Florida
        - Smith Brothers - Real live; Smith Bros, 2000; SR-30455; Smith Brothers (Box 436)
          Catalog # TB2069; A-side Matrix # TB-2069-A WS-CS
        - Smith, Conroy - Dangerous, 1989; SR-30456; Smith, Conroy (Box 436)
          Catalog # RED 1; A-side Matrix # RED-1-A DANGEROUS
          Redman International
        - Smith, Frankie - Double dutch II, 1982; SR-30457; Smith, Frankie (Box 436)
          Catalog # FR-12004; A-side Matrix # FR-12004-A
          Frills Records
        - Smith, Frankie - Teeny-bopper lady, 1981; SR-30458; Smith, Frankie (Box 436)
          Catalog # AS 1315; A-side Matrix # AS 1315S-1A
          WMOT Records
        - Smith, Frankie - Yo-yo champ (from Mississippi), 1982; SR-30459; Smith, Frankie (Box 436)
          Catalog # FR-10001; A-side Matrix # FR-1001-A MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK
        - Smith, Jimmy - The cat, 1964; SR-30460; Smith, Jimmy (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30461. Different discs.
          Catalog # V6-8587; A-side Matrix # V6-8587 S1 64VGS-536 VAN GELDER
          Verve Records
        - Carter, Clarence and Redding, Otis - Soul Christmas, 1968; SR-30461; Carter, Clarence; Redding, Otis; Thomas, Carla; Burke, Solomon; Bell, William; Tex, Joe; Booker T & The MG's; King Curtis (Box 436)
          In same jacket as # SR-30460. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 33-269; A-side Matrix # ST-C-681443-F AT PR-SH
          ATCO Records
        - Smith, Kenny - Tell me something good; Victory shall be mine, 1998; SR-30462; Smith, Kenny (Box 436)
          Catalog # TRN3000CDMR1; A-side Matrix # TRN-3000-LP-P1-A STERLING 2118.1(2)
          Trinity Records
        - Smith, Lonnie - Afro-Desia, 1975; SR-30463; Smith, Lonnie (Box 436)
          Catalog # GM 3308; A-side Matrix # SGM 3308 A-RM FW/NYC ae Brown
          Groove Merchant
        - Smith, Lynette - Only you, 1998; SR-30464; Smith, Lynette (Box 436)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # SLIP 066; A-side Matrix # SLIP 66-A1 -PAULS CUT2-
          Slip 'n' Slide
        - Smith, Michael - Mi cyaan believe it, 1982; SR-30465; Smith, Michael (Box 437)
          Catalog # ILPS 9717; A-side Matrix # ILPS 9717 A-2U-1-1-
        - Smith, Milton - You blow my mind, 1980; SR-30466; Smith, Milton; Stimulus (Box 437)
          Catalog # RD 2016 DJ; A-side Matrix # DRD-2016-C MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
          Roulette
        - Smith, Neddy - Give it up, 1982; SR-30467; Smith, Neddy (Box 437)
          Catalog # DM 924; A-side Matrix # DM 924 B
          Delirium Records
        - Smith, Richard Jon - Don't go walkin' out that door, 1982; SR-30468; Smith, Richard Jon (Box 437)
          Catalog # VJ 12007; A-side Matrix # VJ-12007-SB STERLING EMW
        - Smith, Rick - (We should be) Lovers, 1981; SR-30469; Smith, Rick (Box 437)
          Catalog # BJW 0003; A-side Matrix # A-BJW 0003-MS MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
          Birdie
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Smith, Ronald Louis - Come on and do it; Love talk, 1979; SR-30470; Smith, Ronald Louis (Box 437)
          Catalog # 210; A-side Matrix # SSD-210-A-1 FLA RECORDS
          Sunshine Sound Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Smith, Ronald Louis - Party freaks, come on, 1978; SR-30471; Smith, Ronald Louis (Box 437)
          Catalog # 7803; A-side Matrix # SSE-7803-A SSE MILAN -3
          Sunshine Sound
        - Smith, Toni - (Ooh!) I like the way it feels, 1983; SR-30472; Smith, Toni (Box 437)
          Catalog # EMD-2281; A-side Matrix # EMD-2281-A F/W
          Embassy Records
        - Smith, Wayne - Under me sleng teng, 1985; SR-30473; Smith, Wayne (Box 437)
          Catalog # MM-036; A-side Matrix # MM 036-A
          Witty
        - Smith, Will - Just the two of us, 1998; SR-30474; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # 44 79038; A-side Matrix # XSS-79038-A 1 X F/W GSV
        - Smith, Will - Men in black, 1997; SR-30475; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # CAS 0786; A-side Matrix # XSS 0786 A2 AABAJ
        - Smith, Will - Switch (Reggae remix), 2005; SR-30476; Smith, Will; Elephant Man (Box 437)
          Catalog # INTR-26197-1; A-side Matrix # INTR26197-1A
        - Smith, Will - Will 2k, 1999; SR-30477; Smith, Will; K-Ci (Box 437)
          Catalog # 44 79287; A-side Matrix # XSS 79287A-1B AABAJ
        - Smith, Will - Wild wild west, 1999; SR-30478; Smith, Will; Dru Hill (Box 437)
          Catalog # CAS 40827; A-side Matrix # XSS-40827-A-1B STERLING
        - Smith, Will - Freakin' it, 1999; SR-30479; Smith, Will; DJ Jazzy Jeff & The Fresh Prince (Box 437)
          Catalog # 44 79341; A-side Matrix # XSS 79341A-1A AABAJ
        - Smith, Will - Just cruisin', 1997; SR-30480; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # CAS 3128; A-side Matrix # XSS-3128 A
        - Smith, Will - Gettin' jiggy wit it; Just cruisin', 1997; SR-30481; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # CAS 3543; A-side Matrix # XSS 3543-A2 AABAJ
        - Smith, Will - Miami, 1997; SR-30482; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # CAS 41314; A-side Matrix # XSS 41314 A-1A
        - Smith, Will - Miami, 1998; SR-30483; Smith, Will (Box 437)
          Catalog # 666488 6; A-side Matrix # 1 666488 20 1A1 A
        - Smitty - One time, 2005; SR-30484; Smitty (Box 437)
          Catalog # J12-61157-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-61157-1 SA Ricardo Hit Factory
        - Smitty - One time, 2005; SR-30485; Smitty (Box 437)
        - Smitty "D" - Kic kic, 1986; SR-30486; Smitty "D"; Rock Squad (Box 437)
          In same jacket as # SR-30487. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BR001; A-side Matrix # BR001 A CSB
          Body Rock
        - Smitty "D" - Kic kic, 1986; SR-30487; Smitty "D"; Rock Squad (Box 437)
          In same jacket as # SR-30486. 2 copies.
        - Smoke City - In the world of fantasy, 1985; SR-30488; Smoke City (Box 437)
          Catalog # 49-05336; A-side Matrix # XSS-174915-1B MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Smoked Out Productions - Styles; Bok bok, 1995; SR-30489; Smoked Out Productions (Box 437)
          Catalog # SOP-910; A-side Matrix # 12 SOP-910 -THIS SIDE EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 12G85
          Smoked Out Music
        - Smokester - Westworld; Coastin', 1998; SR-30490; Smokester (Box 437)
          Catalog # SINC12 27; A-side Matrix # SINC 1227 AA
          Smokers Inc.
        - Smokin Suckaz Wit Logic - Playin' foolz, 1993; SR-30491; Smokin Suckaz Wit Logic; Rocker T (Box 437)
          Catalog # E 53448; A-side Matrix # AL 53448-2 STERLING
        - Smokin Suckaz Wit Logic - Mutha made 'em; B4 my rhymez thru, 1993; SR-30492; Smokin Suckaz Wit Logic (Box 437)
          Catalog # EAS 5419; A-side Matrix # XSS5419-1A
        - Smooth - Strawberries, 1998; SR-30493; Smooth; Troutman, Roger; O'Neal, Shaquille; Blaq, Rufus (Box 437)
          Catalog # 31458 2525 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 2525 1A RE1 - WE1 AG
          Perspective Records
        - Smooth - Love & happiness, 1996; SR-30494; Smooth (Box 437)
          Catalog # 31458 7547 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 7547 1A -HUB 1 A&M MASTERING GS
        - Smooth - Away, 1990; SR-30495; Smooth (Box 437)
          Catalog # PW 443; A-side Matrix # PW-443-A 49TW 4-89 587-4 A-1
        - Smooth - Away, 1990; SR-30496; Smooth (Box 437)
        - Smooth B. - Girl he don't love you, 2002; SR-30497; Smooth B. (Box 437)
          Catalog # WOM 3030-1; A-side Matrix # 25-WOM-3030-1 A
          Smooth B Music
        - Smooth, Tim - From the album "Straight up drivin' em", 1994; SR-30498; Smooth, Tim; MC Thick (Box 437)
          Catalog # SPRO 7098; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7098-A S-29259
        - Smoothe Bros. - Drop the beat; Funk you up, 1990; SR-30499; Smoothe Bros. (Box 437)
          Catalog # RT 186-LP; A-side Matrix # RT-186-LP-B
          186 St. Records
        - Smoothe Da Hustler - Hustlin'; Broken language, 1995; SR-30500; Smoothe Da Hustler; Trigger Tha Gambler (Box 437)
          Catalog # PRO-7440-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7440-0-A 1-1 MASTERDISK TD
        - Smoothe Da Hustler - Hustler's theme; Murdafest, 1996; SR-30501; Smoothe Da Hustler; Trigger Tha Gambler; D.V. Alias Khrist (Box 437)
          Catalog # PROFT 449; A-side Matrix # PROFT 449 A-1 DAMONT A